Please remember, my lady.
As for that Qionghua rouge,
you must never touch it again.
Otherwise,
even the immortals
won't be able to save you.
The rouge you requested is ready, madam.
Please take a look.
Why should I believe you?
I
can try it first.
My transformation time,
you already know, madam.
The results will show in 12 hours.
Don't misunderstand, Madam.
It's just the rouge poison acting up.
Madam.
It's been twelve hours.
Her face really hasn't changed at all.
Are there any hidden side effects?
Other than the Qionghua Rouge poison,
there is nothing else.
Hand over the formula.
As long as you
publicly admit
that Yanzhi Pavilion
won first place in the makeup competition,
I will gladly hand over
the formula.
You.
Believe it or not,
I will kill you right now.
You can judge for yourself
whether my life
or this rouge formula
is more
important.
Fine.
I will grant your wish.
Keep a close eye on her.
Don't let anything go wrong.
Yes.
Where did you hide my son?
My Lord.
You bitch!
Where is Yi?
Speak!
I
Where is Yi?
don't know.
Before Yi disappeared,
someone saw him enter Qiwu Courtyard with their own eyes.
How dare you say it has nothing to do with you?
Why is it my fault
that Yi went missing?
Perhaps
he found out something.
Concubine Zhao's...
When you were defeated in battle back then,
the Grand Astrologer said
her astrological sign clashed with yours.
That's why you ordered me to do it.
I am not the only one
who knows about this.
All these years,
he has been investigating the cause of Concubine Zhao's death.
Perhaps his disappearance
means he found something.
My family and I
have done our best
to serve you all these years.
Everything I do is for you, My Lord.
Do you really not understand
my true feelings?
There's no one in the army.
I was too anxious.
Please don't blame me.
Ever since Princess Rong passed away,
her position has been vacant.
But the ancestral sacrifices
cannot be left without someone to preside over them.
Today, I send an envoy with a token of authority
to confer upon you the title of Princess Rong.
May you respectfully accept this ennoblement,
emulate the virtues of the former sages,
bring glory to your family,
be frugal and diligent,
and enjoy everlasting happiness and prosperity.
Respect this.
I bow and thank His Majesty for his grace.
Thank you, Eunuch.
Congratulations, Grand Governor.
Congratulations, Princess.
Your Highness's virtue matches heaven and earth,
and brings blessings to Kuizhou.
Taking advantage of this auspicious time today,
I have another matter to announce.
The winner of the Kuizhou Makeup Selection Ceremony
shall enjoy the honor of five years of exclusive imperial supply.
I respectfully invite the Master of Yanzhi Pavilion
to receive the seal.
Why is she a thin woman?
How can a thin woman sell rouge?
Yeah, who would dare to buy from her?
Fang Zhuozhuo, Master of Yanzhi Pavilion, pays respects to the Princess.
Audacious thin slave,
how dare you impersonate the Master?
Guards!
Fang Qingcheng has already passed the position of Master to me.
This is the Master's succession certificate stamped by the West Market Office.
Please review it, Governor.
It is indeed the official seal of the West Market Office.
Can this skinny woman really be the Master?
This is against the law.
Right?
Do you have a death wish?
How do you think they chose her?
Promoting a thin slave.
The entire West Market Office
should also be punished.
My Lord.
Kuizhou is able to have today
because of strict rule of law.
We absolutely cannot let one thin slave
ruin the rules.
Take this thin slave who has repeatedly violated the Zuirong Teaching
and drag her away.
Governor,
I have something to say.
Take her down and lock her in prison first.
Execute her on a chosen day.
Wait.
After taking this bottle of medicine, one will stop breathing as if dead,
but after twelve hours,
they will recover.
I am here on the special order of Lady Fang
to deliver something to you, Master.
Go back and tell Lady Fang
that I will act according to plan.
Yi'er.
Where have you been these past few days?
You made your father and me worry day and night.
Father once taught me
that those in high positions
should encourage free expression of opinions.
Fang has something to say.
Why can't we wait for her to finish speaking
before deciding whether she is guilty or not?
My Lord.
This Fang
has used Yi'er time and time again,
and shows no respect for the face of our Governor's Mansion.
Such a treacherous and cunning person
must not be allowed to stay here and mislead the public.
Father, why don't you listen
whether this is heresy
or words from the bottom of her heart?
Third Master's words make sense.
It is reasonable and fair.
However, mother, you stop me like this.
Is it because you have a guilty conscience?
But mother,
don't you have a way
to suppress
the wronged ghosts?
Our Commander-in-Chief has always been perceptive.
He will make a fair judgment.
Granted.
My Lord.
Commander-in-Chief, please judge.
Kuizhou's laws never state that a thin woman cannot do business.
A mere Sinful Appearance Cult,
how can it override
Kuizhou's centuries-old laws?
I really don't know
what crime I have committed by doing business according to the law.
Since the Sinful Appearance Cult was implemented,
Kuizhou has had favorable weather.
And people are prosperous.
Back then, the Grand Astrologer
deduced for three months before establishing this cult.
The peace and prosperity over the past ten years
are the best proof.
As a citizen of Kuizhou,
you should obey it.
Peace and prosperity?
How many innocent women in Kuizhou
have suffered because of this cult?
Besides,
there is a thin woman
in a high position in Kuizhou.
And this person is in the Commander-in-Chief's Mansion.
Absurd!
This woman is spreading heresy here.
Men, drag her out!
Commander-in-Chief, do you remember
what Madam Li looked like when she first entered the Mansion?
After a serious illness,
she became plump.
She looks like a different person.
Don't you find it strange?
I have a rouge here
that can solve your doubts.
Rouge?
Yeah.
How can it solve doubts?
Rouge?
My Lord.
This bitch
is trying to drive a wedge between us.
What she holds
must be poison.
Do you know
what a serious crime it is
to frame the Princess?
It's about time.
Madam.
This...
Monster! Monster!
Protect the Commander-in-Chief!
My face!
How dare you lie to me!
Rouge!
Where is the rouge?
Where is it?
Madam.
Bitch!
I'll kill you!
Kill you!
This is the secret Qionghua Rouge from the Western Regions.
It only works on specific women.
By using this rouge,
Madam's appearance
can instantly change from gaunt to plump.
Madam used this exact item
to deceive the Commander
and the people of Kuizhou for over ten years.
You...
Why did you have to do this?
This Qionghua Rouge
is highly toxic.
Every time the poison flares up,
I suffer
bone-piercing pain.
But I
gladly endure it.
Because I know
it is all for
you, My Lord.
My Lord.
What I have done for you, My Lord,
is far more than this.
Shut up!
It was your own
obsession.
It has nothing to do
with me.
Twenty years of marriage,
and it comes to this.
This rouge
is wonderfully toxic.
It poisons me so much
that I
see those evil spirits coming for my life.
Especially her.
Why are you here?
Don't come closer!
I didn't kill you!
It wasn't me! Don't come closer!
Don't come closer!
I didn't kill you!
It wasn't me!
Crazy woman.
Catch her!
My Lord.
Women each have their own beauty.
Why break your pride
for others?
Nature has its own beauty;
why seek validation from others?
Your bone-piercing pain
wasn't brought by the rouge.
It's your own making.
You insisted on making this world
force all women
into the same mold,
including yourself.
You...
My Lord.
Yi.
Do you want to know
how your mother died?
Come here,
let Mother tell you.
My mother's death...
Come.
Lady Li!
Harboring a monster,
murdering innocent people,
and bringing chaos to Kuizhou.
Execute her immediately.
Take her
to the mass grave.
Please be wise, Governor.
I risk my life to advise you again.
In the name of the Zuirong Cult, Lady Li
not only publicly executed thin women,
but also caused all the ladies in Kuizhou
to harm themselves for the beauty of plumpness.
Some took weight-gain drugs
for three consecutive months,
leading to heart failure.
Some were force-fed
until their stomachs burst.
How is this beauty?
This is clearly a murder weapon.
This is the list of deceased victims
of the Zuirong Cult that I investigated secretly.
Two hundred and nineteen people,
every one of them with a name.
Bring it up.
To think such a tragedy has happened.
I implore you, Governor,
to abolish this evil decree.
Announce to all of Kuizhou that
the beauty of a woman
lies not in being plump or thin,
but in the brilliance of her character.
Let the ladies of Kuizhou be beautiful in their own way.
This action
will not only comfort the souls of these over 200 victims
in heaven,
but also establish your reputation for benevolent governance.
Granted.
From today on,
the Zuirong Cult is abolished.
For all women in Kuizhou,
their worth will no longer be judged by their figure.
You are wise, Governor.
Let's go see.
The notice!
Let me see.
By the order of the Governor,
the Zuirong Cult
violates human nature
and is abolished effective immediately.
From this day on,
the women of Kuizhou,
whether plump or thin,
can all pursue their own ambitions.
Great!
It's canceled.
It really is.
I can walk on the streets openly from now on!
I no longer need to wear this junk every day to pretend to be fat!
Wonderful!
3 days later.